autumn jung

autumnkangas@gmail.com · 312-888-0342

GitHub: AutumnJ · Website: autumnj.github.io

TECHNICAL SKILLS

LANGUAGES

JavaScript

Ruby

Python

HTML

CSS

SOL

FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

Ruby on Rails

Sinatra

iQuery

React

Redux

Bootstrap

Django

TESTING

RSpec

Mocha

Capybara

PERSISTENCE

SQLite

PostgreSQL

OTHER

Git, Sublime Text, Fiddler, Postman, PythonAnywhere Full stack web developer with a passion for natural and programming languages. With experience in Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, and React, and a background in office management, I discovered web development while working at various tech startups. I bring strong skills in project management and a desire for iterative innovation, which helps companies provide the best product and experience to their clients and employees.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

PETS SEEKING PEOPLE

GitHub | Ruby Gem

Command line interface scraper gem to locate cats and dogs available for adoption by geographic location

- Scraped ASPCA website with Nokogiri and bundled results into CLI gem
- Published to RubyGems (900+ downloads)

COMMUNITY LIBRARY

GitHub | Demo

Rails application for tracking books in your library, and lending or borrowing books from others

- Built application with MVC pattern and internal API, using Rails and JavaScript to power the front end
- Used OmniAuth for OAuth authentication via GitHub and Devise for authenticating other users
- Leveraged ¡Query and JavaScript for AJAX functionality

ADOPT A PET

GitHub | Demo

Gamified adoptable pet search interface with React front end and Rails back end

- Incorporated user inputs into external API request (Petfinder) and persisted returned data to internal Rails API
- Managed application state with Redux
- Used Bootstrap's React-Bootstrap implementation for design elements

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

JELLYVISION - Chicago, IL

Software Quality Assurance Contractor | 9/2017-12/2017

- Executed cross browser and mobile device testing for Flash and HTML-based applications
- Verified required functionality and customizations based on client-specific healthcare and benefits enrollment options
- Compiled detailed bug report documentation and worked with development team (using JIRA and confluence) to test subsequent fixes

CONFERENCES

Google Women Techmakers Women's Day Summit MARCH 2018

GOTO Chicago Software Developer Conference APRIL 2018

REVIEWTRACKERS - Chicago, IL

Office Manager | 7/2017-9/2017

- Created and implemented operational budget for office events, supplies, services, and amenities
- Provided executive support for VP of Operations, COO and CEO of tech startup with 50+ employees

HEALTHCARE RESEARCH (MYCNAJOBS) - Chicago, IL Office Manager and Executive Assistant to CEO | 5/2015-7/2017

- Managed all incoming revenue, including executing accounts receivable and payable tasks in QuickBooks, processing and scheduling recurring credit card payments and implementing client-specific collections procedures
- Administered payroll and benefits for healthcare tech startup as it grew from 10 to 35 employees
- Moved HR documentation for all past and present employees to online platform (BambooHR) to reduce liability
- Used Zoho and HubSpot CRMs to manage client records
- Built wireframes with Mockflow and performed requirements mapping for creation of proprietary CRM and billing system

RAVENSWOOD HEALTH AND WELLNESS CENTER - Chicago, IL Office Manager and Chiropractic Assistant | 2/2014-5/2015

- Created and implemented employee manual and training procedures for 10 chiropractic assistants
- Managed weekly schedule of 200+ appointments while providing administrative support to chiropractors and registered nurse
- Handled all payments for practice, including verifying insurance coverage, communicating payment plans and issuing invoices

CP HOMES/PACRIM INTERNATIONAL CAPITAL - Shenzhen, China Assistant to the General Manager's Office | 7/2012-3/2013

- Utilized Mandarin Chinese skills to assist Chinese-speaking HR team in their efforts to recruit an English-speaking lawyer
- Translated company policies from Chinese to English
- Compiled monthly client-facing newsletter and translated articles from English to Mandarin Chinese
- Prepared clients for the EB-5 visa process by conducting mock interviews
- Researched and compiled location-specific transition materials to prepare Chinese clients for a successful cultural, economic and social transition to the United States

EDUCATION

FLATIRON SCHOOL

Full Stack Web Development Program | 2018

• Women Take Tech Scholarship Recipient

SHENZHEN UNIVERSITY

Shenzhen, China

Certificate: Chinese Language | 2011-2012

LIBERTY UNIVERSITY ONLINE

Bachelor of Arts in Biblical Studies | 2011

• Graduated Summa Cum Laude